{
    "id": "kakitaibuki",
    "name": "Kakita Ibuki",
    "yomi": "カキタイブキ",
    "text": [
        "空間にとらわれる人。小さいほど大きい何かを探しています。",
        "A person who are swayed by a space.<br>I'm looking for something that is bigger when it's smaller."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Instagram",
            "href": "https://www.instagram.com/_kaaaaa__/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Do you often experience deja vu?",
            "jp": "普段デジャブを体験スル？",
            "yes": "Yes i do",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Which do you believe?",
            "jp": "信じるとしたら",
            "yes": "your own memory",
            "left": "自分の記憶",
            "no": "someone's memory",
            "right": "他人の記憶"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Well.. it might be",
            "jp": "きっとそうだろうな",
            "yes": "Yes it might be",
            "left": "はい、きっと。",
            "no": "No... may be...",
            "right": "いいえ、おそらく。"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Is it that?",
            "jp": "あれはそれ？",
            "yes": "Yes that is it",
            "left": "はい、あれはそれ。",
            "no": "No it is that",
            "right": "いいえ、それはあれ。"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "There is a thing that only i can see",
            "jp": "自分にしか見えないものがある",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "To be honest you see the magical power?",
            "jp": "実は魔力が見える",
            "yes": "Yes i do",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Which would you choose?",
            "jp": "なんとなく選ぶとしたら",
            "yes": "three",
            "left": "木 (き)",
            "no": "mountain",
            "right": "山 (やま)"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Things are filled with memories?",
            "jp": "思い出はモノに詰まってる？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Does it remind you that time?",
            "jp": "それを見たらあの時を思いだす",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Where is memory do you think?",
            "jp": "記憶ってどこにあるの？",
            "yes": "brain/heart/body",
            "left": "脳・心・身体",
            "no": "things/space/environment",
            "right": "モノ・空間・環境"
        }
    ]
}